♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Jean?
Yea!
Ezra? Clare? Lola?
Yep, double yea.
Huh?
So you’ve dated every girl
in the 8th grade?
Everyone except Heidi Klinger.
Are you trying to set a record or something?
No way. I’m just searching for true love.
Well, look who’s here, my dear Ulrich…
Wanna go see a movie with me this afternoon?
That would depend on what’s playing…
Adventure In The Tropics…
Oh no, what a bummer.
I’ve already seen it. Shame.
I’ll go see it with you!
See what?
The film!
Great! Let’s go then!
Hey, do you mean that?
Not!
(LAUGHING)
(GROWLING)
You actually went to see Adventure In The Tropics?
You crazy?
I’d rather study for a math quiz
than to go to the movies with Sissi.
You make me sick, Stern!
You really think you’re hot stuff,
I’m gonna knock that smile right off your face!
Oh yeah? Well go on then.
What are you waiting for?
(SCREAMING)
Ouch, now that, has gotta hurt.
(INAUDIBLE MUMBLING)
What?
I said jealousy makes people go bananas!
Yeah, and love plays tricks with your mind.
Right! I gotta go and get Aelita.
I promised to give her my croissants.
She likes croissants with her hot chocolate.
What were you saying about love?
What does it do to peoples minds?
Looks like there are no exceptions to the rule.
Speaking of hot chocolate, I gotta get moving.
I finally got a date with Heidi.
You’re gonna give her your croissants?
You must be joking!
A guy’s gotta eat, doesn’t he?
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Hi Jeremie, you haven’t seen Odd have you?
He promised to have breakfast with me.
Huh?
I can’t believe that!
Hey there Yumi.
Say you wouldn’t have the answers
to the math quiz, would you?
Huh!
Oh wow…
I sure am glad brushed my teeth this morning!
Huh?
Jeremie, would you mind telling me
why you kissed me in front of Odd?
What are you talking about?
Are you out of your mind?
Aelita!
Oh no.
Hey everyone,
Slide over and make me some room!
Don’t you wanna sit with Heidi?
She’s all by herself.
Hm?
Listen, I don’t know what all this is about,
but I swear to you that, uh…
You know something?
You sure threw me a real curveball there Mr. Romantic…
But, I…
Guess you won’t be needing this croissant.
Later.
Hey Ulrich, glad I ran into you.
In case you haven’t heard the latest news,
Yumi’s going out with Mathias Durrell.
What?
Morning everyone!
Hey, thanks Ulrich!
So, you really like Durrell, do you?
He’s a nice guy, why?
How does he kiss, huh?
Kiss? How should I know?
Cut out the acting Yumi, William saw you.
I saw you.
Huh? What?
Hm?
Uh, rumor has it I’m dating Mathias Durrell.
No kidding?
Well rumor has it I kissed Heidi Klinger.
Croissant?
I’m not hungry.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Ulrich will never go out with you.
He said so, I heard him!
Hey, speak of the devil, there he is!
Why don’t you ask him yourself?
Hey!
Hehe, what were you saying?
How does he do it?
What does he have that I don’t?
Everything.
Except for your gross pimples.
I dare you to say that again!
Hey Yumi, everything okay?
(BELL RINGING)
Yes, right. Last time we were
discussing the causes of World War I.
Aelita, can we talk?
We’re in class.
Why did you kiss Heidi?
I did not kiss Heidi.
I saw you.
It wasn’t a very nice thing to do to Odd.
Then what about you?
Kissing Sissi to get back at Yumi, you call that nice?
What?
I didn’t kiss Sissi.
I saw you.
And now my first question is,
when did Galleani die?
Well class, I’m waiting…
Ulrich, wphen did Galleani die?
Well, uh at the end of his life?
(LAUGHTER)
Stern? What are you doing here?
You should be in class.
Huh?
Oh, is that you Yolanda?
Hey.
Hey, Aelita!
Jeremie?
You wanted to talk to me?
Yeah, let’s talk about you and Nicholas.
Huh?
I sure hope he’s better at kissing than he is at math.
What are you talking about?
I never kissed Nicholas!
I don’t believe this!
First you kiss the biggest loser in the whole school,
and then you lie about it?
But, Jeremie?
Trust me.
Incredible, you make a fool of me in public.
Then you lie to me,
and now you expect me trust you?
How could you do that?
You really let me down.
You have no idea how much either.
Oh no.
I’m telling you, I never kissed Sissi!
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello?
XANA’s attacking!
Okay, let’s meet in the park!
Hello, this is Aelita.
Leave me a message.
Right, I can explain everything.
All this kissing is another one of XANA’s schemes that--
That doesn’t make any sense, he can’t control us.
I know that, but I also know that I did not kiss Heidi,
so there must be a Jeremie clone somewhere.
And a Yumi clone.
And an Ulrich clone also.
Right, and I bet they’re all just
one big polymorphic clone.
A poly-what?
A polymorphic clone,
it can change its appearance at will.
XANA must have sent a kind of ghost
that look like anyone it wants to.
But why?
To make trouble in our group,
to divide and conquer.
XANA’s really smart,
not like us.
I guess Odd was right,
jealousy makes people crazy.
Listen, we gotta go to Lyoko
to solve this. Hey, where’s Aelita?
Gone, and all because of me.
Oh bravo, where did she go?
Hm… I think I might know.
Aelita?
Jeremie?
I’m really sorry Aelita.
You’re... not angry with me anymore?
No, I figured it out.
You see XANA was using a polymorph
that can change its appearance at will.
So you didn’t really kiss Heidi?
No. Let’s go now.
We have to get to the factory fast.
You’re not too upset with me, are you?
Let’s go!
Aelita!
Jeremie? But...
It’s Xana!
He made a clone of me to trick you.
Don’t listen to him Aelita, he’s Xana!
If I’ve got this straight,
one of these two is the poly-dorking clone, right?
The polymorphic clone, Odd.
Aelita, trust me.
Don’t listen to him, I’m the real Jeremie!
You know I am, I kissed you.
That’s right.
The real Jeremie would not have kissed me like that.
Keep your hands off her!
Quick! To the factory!
You guys go on,
I’ll take care of him.
Oh no, not the big tough guy.
Head for the scanners.
I’m launching the virtualization process.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Aelita.
Transfer Ulrich.
Scanner Yumi.
Scanner Aelita.
Scanner Ulrich.
Virtualization!
The tower isn’t far away,
direction North, North-East.
There, across the bridge!
Hey, Xana?
If you’re gonna keep changing appearances like that,
do me a favor and turn into a wimp next time.
Oh no, not him, I know his kind,
small but tough as nails.
Hurry up!
Aelita, head for the tower.
I’ll take care of them.
What did I tell ya?
Xana’s sending a monster!
You’re almost there, Aelita!
Supersprint!
Ulrich!
Let’s swap monsters.
Okay.
Here we go.
Careful Yumi, at ten o’clock!
I’ll materialize the Overwing.
Thanks Jeremie.
Careful, behind you Ulrich!
Hornets!
Yumi!
Aelita! Hurry up!
I’m nearly there!
Jeremie!
I’m trapped.
Why isn’t this elevator working?
Ulrich! The scyphozoa is attacking Aelita.
Forget about the monster for now.
Hey, it’s no picnic out here!
You okay Yumi?
Jeremie, I’m gonna need the Overbike!
You got it, Ulrich.
Don’t worry Yumi, we’ll manage.
Okay poly-whatever.
I’m gonna transform you now!
Devirtualization.
Hey Jeremie, what’s going on?
Jeremie?
Answer me!
What’d you do to him?
Yumi!
Odd, help me it’s Xana.
You’re not gonna believe this polymorph, are you?
Odd no, cut it out peabrain.
I’m the real Yumi.
Yeah right, you expect me to fall for that old one!
On three, we pulverize you.
1, 2, 3
Jeremie, you’ve gotta wake up.
Ulrich, hurry up.
Aelita’s hardly got any memory left.
Drop her, fishface!
You okay Aelita?
Aelita?
I’m… I’m okay.
Well I’m not feeling so great.
Aelita, quick!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Tower deactivated.
That’s very sweet of you Jim,
but as I already told you I’m engaged to be married.
But if that’s true Yolanda,
uhh why’d you kiss me?
I, kissed you?
You should get some rest Jim.
Now be a good boy,
and let me take your temperature, alright?
How did you guess I was the real Yumi?
Because you called me peabrain,
Xana would never call me that.
He’s got too much… respect for me.
Oh no, Xana just doesn’t know you
as well as Yumi does.
Jeremie,
would you come with me for a minute?
I’d like to check something, you mind?
No, go ahead.
Check what?
I knew it.
Uhh, Jeremie come back to Earth.
Let’s hope that XANA leaves us alone for a little while.
I think Jeremie’s gonna need
some time to get over that one, huh guys?
(LAUGHTER)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS